我是坐到什么东西了啊
What am I sitting on?
世界顶端  河堤码头(歌词)
Top of the world? Dock of the bay?
想不出来了
I'm out.
好恶心  内裤
Ew-eww!! Undies!
快说  谁的
All right! Who's are they?
谁的
Who's are they?
不是我的
Well, they're not mine!
是乔伊的  一定是他的
Well, they're Joey's! They gotta be Joey's!
的确是我的
Yeah, they're mine.
看吧  就是乔伊的  乔...伊的
See? They're Joey's! J-J-J-J-J-Joey's!
怎么会在这里
Why are they here?
我不知道
I don't know uhh...
因为我是乔伊
Well, I'm Joey.
我生性龌龊
Yeah, I'm disgusting,
随便在别人家脱内裤
I take my underwear off in other people's homes.
快拿走  你哪里出问题了
Well, get'em out of here! What's wrong with you?
-就是  -就是
- Yeah! - Yeah!
拿去啊
Take'em!
乔伊  你干嘛不敢碰  这是你的内裤
Joey, you can touch them! They're  underwear.
钱德勒  借一步说话
Chandler? A word.
我受够了  不想再帮你们说谎了
That's it! I'm tired of covering for you two!
这种事不能再发生了
This has got to stop!
而且还是白色三角裤  你八岁吗
And tighty-whiteys! What are you, 8?
谢谢你  乔伊  感激不尽
Thank you Joey, thank you so much!
我家不欢迎你  我讨厌这样
Oh hey, no, you're not welcome. Okay, look, I hate this!
你们害我不断出丑
You guys keep embarrassing me!
昨天瑞秋在这边浴室看到你的剃刀
Yesterday, Rachel found your razor in our bathroom
我不知道怎么回答  只好说是我的
and I didn't know what to say, so I said it was mine
我要扮演一个女人
and-and that I was playing a woman in a play.
结果还得一不做二不休
And one thing led to another and
连脚踝周围都剃光了  那里很难刮
Wow! And around the ankles, y'know that is a tough spot.
没错  告诉你们  我不能...
Yeah, it was! All right, listen, I can't...
我们要说谎也不好受
All this lying has been hard on us too.
是嘛  我瞧你们上床挺享受的
Oh-oh, yeah-yeah, I bet all the sex makes it easier!
那倒是
Well, yeah actually.
我们以后一定会更小心的
We'll try to be more careful okay?
只是  我们不想告诉大家
It's just that, we don't want everyone to know
因为我们实在太甜蜜了
because this is going really well,
有可能就是保密才能这么顺利
and maybe the reason it's going really well is because it's a secret.
我知道听起来很怪
I know it sounds really weird,
但我们都不太会处理感情问题
but we're just so bad at relationships.
没错  帮帮忙
We are! Help us!
拜托
Help!
好吧  不过你要跟我上床一次
All right! But,  you do it with me once.
乔伊
Joey!
就知道你不肯
Didn't think so.
菲比
Phoebe.
菲比  你在看什么
Hi, pheebs. What are you reading?
《呼啸山庄》
Umm, Wethering Heights.
我在新学院大学上文学课
I'm taking a literature class at the New School
明天第一节课之前必须看完
and I have to finish it for the first session tomorrow.
我不知道你在上课  太棒了
I didn't know you were taking a class. That is so cool.
上次的拉马兹分娩呼吸课很好玩
Yeah! Well, I really liked that Lamaze class I took!
所以这次我决定换个
Y'know and this time I thought I'd go for something,
要用脑的  期末考又不用那么痛的课
y'know a little more intellectual, with a less painful final exam.
亲爱的  听起来很有意思
Honey that sounds like fun.
你也可以一起来
Yeah! Ooh, you should come with me!
-那就有人可以跟我一起坐了  -好的
- Oh yeah, then I'd have someone to sit with! - Okay.
太好了  不过你有时间看书吗
Yeah! Okay-ooh, but are you going to have time to read it?
我高中时就看过了
Oh, I read that in high school.
一定很好玩的
This is going to be so much fun!
安静  先让我看完
Okay-shhh, I have to finish.
-大家好  -你怎么啦  哥们
- Hi. - What's wrong buddy?
有同事偷吃了我的三明治
Someone at work ate my sandwich!
警察怎么说
Well, what did the police say?
那是感恩节剩下的三明治
My Thanksgiving leftover sandwich.
竟然给人偷吃掉了
I can't believe someone ate it!
罗斯  不过是个三明治而已
Ross, it's just a sandwich!
不过是个三明治
Just a sandwich?
我今年三十岁了
Look, I am 30 years old,
已经离婚两次  还无家可归
I'm gonna be divorced twice and I just got evicted!
那个三明治是我人生中唯一美好的东西
That sandwich was the only good thing going on in my life!
结果唯一美好的东西竟然给人偷吃了
Someone ate the only good thing going on in my life!
我还有食材可以再做一个三明治
Okay, look, I-I have enough stuff for one more sandwich,
我本来是准备自己吃的  但是...
I mean I was going to eat it myself, but...
太好了  真是谢谢你
That-that would be incredible. Thank you so much.
我还是不敢相信有人偷吃了
I still can't believe someone ate it!
看  我还留了一张纸条在上面
I-I !! I mean, look, I left a note and everything.
咚咚咚  谁啊  罗斯·盖勒的午餐
Knock-knock. Who's there? Ross Geller's lunch.
哪个罗斯·盖勒的午餐
Ross Geller's lunch, who?
这是罗斯·盖勒的午餐
Ross Geller's lunch,
请勿偷走我  好吗
please don't take me. Okay?
奇怪你居然没有把午饭顶在头上回家
I'm surprised you didn't go home wearing your lunch.
不想让别人偷吃你的东西
Okay, look you wanna hold onto your food?
那就得吓跑他们
You gotta scare people off.
这是我在街头流浪时学到的
I learned that living on the street.
是嘛  你会怎么说  菲比
Really?! So what would you say Pheebs?
是不是说  脏爪子少碰我的饭饭
Stuff like uh, "Keep your mitts off my grub?"
罗斯  你以为菲比在街上演
Say Ross, when you picture Phoebe living on the street,
《孤女安妮》吗
is she surrounded by the entire cast of Annie?
放上这张纸条就没人敢偷吃了
Okay, this will keep them away from your stuff.
菲比  你真狠
Phoebe, you are a bad ass!
下次再告诉你们  我拿刀捅条子的事
Someday I'll tell you about the time I stabbed the cop.
-菲比  -是他先捅我的
- Phoebe? - Well, he stabbed me first!!
勃朗特姐妹是那个时代的杰出女性
The Brontie sisters were really remarkable women for their time.
她们生活在男权社会
They lived in a patriarchal society.
抱歉我迟到了  因为我太晚出门
Sorry I'm late, but I left late.
好吧
Okay.
菲比  这本书讲什么的
So Pheebs, what is the book about?
你不是高中时看过吗
I thought you said you read it in high school.
后来我想起来  我当时尝试去看
Well yeah, but then I remembered I started it
正好碰上啦啦队有活动
and there was this pep rally and I was,
我又是叠罗汉队形的最上面一个  总之
I was on top of the pyramid but anyway-
这本书到底讲什么的
What is this book about?
讲的是凯瑟琳跟希斯克利夫的爱情悲剧
Okay, umm, it's this tragic love story between Cathy and Heathcliff
故事发生在英国令人毛骨悚然的荒野
and umm, it takes place on like these really creepy moors in England.
我想这象征着希斯克利夫性格中的野性
Which I think represents the wildness of Heathcliff's character.
我对象征主义很有一套
I totally get symbolism.
这本书的主题是什么
How would you characterize the theme of this book,
看看找谁  瑞秋·格林
uh let's see here , Rachel Green?
我得说  这是一个爱情悲剧
Umm, well I would have to say that it's a, it's tragic love story.
显而易见
Well, that's sort of a given,
不过没错  还有人补充吗
but yes. Anyone else?
还有  象征主义
Oh-oh-oh, symbolism!
荒野的环境
And uh, the-the uh, wildness of the moors,
我认为反映了
which I think is-is mirrored
希斯克利夫性格中狂野的一面
in the wildness of Heathcliff's character.
回答得很好  瑞秋读得相当透彻
Excellent! What Rachel has shrewdly observed here...
你盗用了我的答案
You completely stole my answer!
亲爱的  这不是明摆着吗
Well, honey that was pretty obvious.
但你怎么会知道  你压根没看过
Well how would you know?! You didn't even read it!
你怎么看  穿蓝衬衫的同学
What do you think? You in the blue shirt.
我认为这个问题  有很多可能的答案
I think that uh, yours is a question with many possible answers.
那你愿意大胆说一个吗
Would ya care to venture one?
你愿意大胆说一个吗
Would you care to venture one?
你是在重复我的话吗
Are you just repeating what I'm saying?
好吧  我们继续
All right, let's move on.
好的
Okay then.
你为什么不直接说你没看过
Yeah but why didn't you just say that you didn't read the book?!
我不希望他认为我很蠢
Because I didn't want him to think I was stupid!
你当时的样子好丢人
I mean, that was really embarrassing what happened to you!
菲比
Phoebe!
菲比  你那张纸条  效果神奇
Phoebe! Your note, amazing!
不但没人敢碰我的三明治
Not only did no one touch my sandwich,
而且同事都对我敬畏三分
but people at work are actually afraid of me.
还有人叫我疯子  疯子盖勒
Yeah, a guy called me mental! Mental Geller,
我一直梦想有这种超酷外号
yeah, I always wanted a cool nickname like that.
高中时你最酷的外号就是"尿裤子盖勒"
Yeah, the best you got in high school was Wet Pants Geller.
那是饮水器弄的
That was the water fountain! Okay?!
反正
Anyway,
大家帮我写报告
people are writing reports for me,
为配合我的日程安排而推迟截止日期
pushing back deadlines to fit my schedule,
告诉你们  原来对人耍狠
I'm telling you, you get tough with people
就可以呼风唤雨
you can get anything you want.
崔比安尼  把咖啡给我  马上
Hey Tribbiani, give me that coffee! Now!
今天真有意思
God, this was really fun!
我本来还在猜你会不会约我
I've been wondering if you even gonna ask me out.
那你还在猜吗
So you uh, still wondering?
不  我们已经约会啦
No, we just went out.
你真聪明  我喜欢
You're smart. I like that.
蜡烛
Oh, candles!
那是什么  毯子  摄像机
What is that? A blanket? A video camera?
-我的天啊  -别误会  别走
- Oh my God! - Oh no-no-no-no, wait-wait-wait!!
真不敢相信  你居然以为
I can't believe you thought that
第一次约会就可以拍下我们上床的过程
you're gonna video tape us having sex on the first date!
乔伊  她刚说的
Joey, is what she just said umm-
天啊  你还真打算...
Oh my God.  You were actually gonna...
这是怎么回事
What is going on here?
而且钱德勒还在家
And with Chandler in the next room.
你是变态吗
What are you, what are you sick?
因为我是乔伊
I'm Joey.
我是说  我生性龌龊
I mean, I'm disgusting.
还拍低成本的黄片
I make low-budget adult films.
你们答应我会更小心的
You guys promised you'd be more careful!
有没有搞错
I mean, come on!
乔伊的好名声都给你们毁了
The good Joey name is being dragged through the mud here!
太对不起了
We're so sorry.
我要把你们的事情说出去
Well, I'm telling everyone about you!
这样才能解释内裤  摄像机
That's the only way to explain the underwear and the video camera
我才不会被当作变态
that doesn't make me look like a pig!
不  你可以有更好的解释
No-no, wait! There's got to be a better explanation.
告诉他们你必须拍黄片
You can tell them you had to make an adult film
因为你在上黄片课
for your...adult film class.
这理由还不错  但是不行
Yeah, I like that. But no-no,
瑞秋在你们家发现我的内裤又怎么解释
how does that explain why Rachel found my underwear at your place?
不知道
Oh-I don't know.
看来你们得出柜承认你们的地下情了
Well, get ready to come out of the non-gay closet!
请再等等  我保证一定会想出理由
Okay, just wait, please. I promise we'll come up with something.
再给我们点时间
Just give us a little more time.
好吧  最好让我面上非常有光
All right. Hey, but it better make me look really, really good.
还有  摄像机这招
Oh, and another thing, the video camera?
真高
Nice!!
罗斯  可以跟你谈谈吗
Umm, Ross. May I have a word with you?
当然  唐纳德
Yeah, of course, Donald.
有同事抱怨你
We've been getting reports of
最近脾气火爆
some very angry behavior on your part.
什么
What?!
写恐吓信  拒绝遵守截稿期限
Threatening letters, refusal to meet deadlines,
很显然现在大家叫你疯子
apparently people now call you mental.
是啊
Yeah.
我们希望你找精神科医生谈谈
We want you to speak to a psychiatrist.
你不懂  其实是误会
Oh no, you-you don't understand.
太傻了
Ugh, this is so silly.
一切要从我的三明治说起
Umm, this is all because of a sandwich.
三明治
A sandwich?
是的  我妹妹
Yeah. You see my-my sister
非常会做火鸡三明治
makes these amazing turkey sandwiches.
她的秘诀是
Her secret is, she puts a,
多夹一片浸过肉汁的面包
an extra slice of gravy soaked bread in the middle;
我称之为"多汁大帝"
I call it the Moist Maker.
有一次我把三明治放在冰箱
Anyway, I-I put my sandwich in the fridge over here...
-你知道吗  -什么
- Oh, you know what? - What?
对不起  应该是我吃掉了
I-I'm sorry. I, I-I-I believe I ate that.
你吃了我的三明治
You ate my sandwich?
我一时看错  谁都可能拿错
It was a simple mistake. It could happen to anyone.
是吗
Oh-oh really?
难道你的
Did you confuse it
火鸡三明治也有"多汁大帝"吗
with your own turkey sandwich with a Moist Maker?
没有
No.
你记不记得
Do you perhaps remember
上面有张字条
seeing a note on top of it?
我以为那是有人开玩笑或是打油诗
There may have been a-a joke or a limerick of some kind.
上面写着  那是我的三明治
That said it was my sandwich?!
你别激动
Now-now calm down.
到我办公室找找  可能垃圾筒里还有剩
Come look in my office, some of it may still be in the trash.
什么
What?
那个三明治很大
Well, it was quite large.
我不得不扔掉了大部分
I-I-I-I-I had to throw most of it away.
你把我的三明治扔掉了
You-you-you-you threw my sandwich away!
我的三明治
My sandwich?!!!
今天这本书讲什么的
So umm, what's this book about?
你又没看吗
You didn't read this one either?!
本来想看的  后来看别的去了
Well, I was gonna, but I accidentally read something else.
-看了什么  -《时尚》
- What? - Vogue!
跟我讲讲这个叫简·爱的女人
Hey, so tell me about this Jane Eyre woman.
不讲  你应该自己看
No! You should've read it yourself!
拜托  菲比  别这么假正经嘛
Come on Phoebe! Don't be such a goodie-goodie!
好吧
Fine!
听好了  简·爱呢  首先
Okay, all right, so Jane Eyre, first of all,
你会以为她是女人  其实不然
you'd think she's a woman, but she's not.
她是生化人
She's a cyborg.
生化人  就是机器人吗
A cyborg?! Isn't that like a robot?!
这本书在当时超级先进
Yeah, this book was light years ahead of its time.
抱歉我迟到了  开始上课吧
Sorry I'm late. Let's get started.
大家对《简·爱》有何感想
So, what did everybody think about Jane Eyre?
瑞秋刚跟我讨论过
Umm, Rachel and I were just discussing it
她有些非常有趣的见解
and she actually had some very interesting insights.
请说  瑞秋
Well, go ahead Rachel.
谢谢你  菲比
Uh, thank you Phoebe.
《简·爱》最让我震惊的就是
Umm, well, what struck me most when reading Jane Eyre
这本书领先于它的时代
was uh, how the book was so ahead of its time.
如果你指的是女权主义  这么说也对
If you're talking about feminism, I think you're right.
当然有女权主义  不过还有机器人
Yeah, well, feminism yes, but also the robots.
既然上次咱们的小电影没拍成
Okay, so umm, since that video camera thing didn't work out
我就先给你来点预告片好了
uh, I thought that I would give you just a little preview.
你没穿衣服
You're naked in this picture!
我知道
I know.
罗斯
Ross.
钱德勒
Chandler.
莫妮卡
Monica.
罗斯  你没事吧
Ross, are you okay?
我很好  今天上班时去看过精神科医生
I'm fine! I saw a psychiatrist at work today.
为什么
Why?!
因为我脾气太暴躁
On account of my rage.
而且最近越来越严重
Which I may say, right now, is out of control.
他让我吃了药
He gave me a pill for it.
-吃药  -是啊
- A pill? - Uh-huh.
当医生说我应该请假
Well, when the psychiatrist told me I had to take a leave of absence
因为我对上司大吼大叫时
because I yelled at my boss
我又开始暴跳如雷
I started to get worked up again,
所以他要我吃颗镇定药
so he offered me a tranquilizer.
我觉得这主意不错  所以就吃了
And I thought was a good idea so, I took it.
等等  他们逼你请假吗
Wait a minute, they're making you take time off work?
而且你也同意吗
And you're okay with that?
我不知道  不工作的话刚开始可能不习惯
I don't know. It's going to be weird not having a job for a while,
不过我已经不在乎三明治了
but I, I definitely don't care about my sandwich.
丢死人了
Ugh, that was so embarrassing!
你竟然还让我不停地说下去
I can't believe you let me go on and on like that!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你把简·爱与机械战警作比较实在太好笑了
It was just so funny when you started comparing Jane Eyre to Robocop.
一点也不好笑
That was not funny!
我太生气了  你根本不想好好上课
Well, I snapped! Okay? You weren't taking the class seriously.
菲比  拜托  这有什么了不起的
Phoebe, come on! What is the big deal?
我以为我们就是一起出去
I thought this was going to be something we could do together!
上课打发时间闹着玩
Y'know, I thought it would be fun!
好玩很重要  但是我也想学点东西
Well, yeah! Fun is good, but y'know I also wanted to learn.
大家老说在高中
Y'know, people are always talking about
学东学西  我却没上过高中
what they learned in high school and I never went to high school.
所以你真心想上课
Oh, so you really wanted to learn.
你知道吗  菲比  我只想找点乐子
Yeah, y'know, Pheebs I just wanted to have fun.
你知道你该拉谁去吗
Ohh, you know who you should go with?
我知道...
I know! I know! I know!
莫妮卡  这问题是你问的
Monica, you asked the question.
天啊  这是莫妮卡
Oh my God! That's Monica!!
不是的  不是的
Oh no-no-no! No-no-no-no-no-no-no!
滚远点  你这个变态狂
You get away from me!! You sick, sick, sick, sick-o!!
怎么啦
What's going on?
乔伊有个秘密偷窥孔
Joey has got a secret peephole!
不不不
Oh no! No! No! No!
他有  他拍了莫妮卡的裸照
Yes! He has a naked picture of Monica!
他拍下我们的裸照
He takes naked pictures of us!
还一边吃鸡块一边看
And then he eats chicken and looks at them!
看
Look!
喂  这是我老妹
Dude! That's my sister!
给我
Give me that!
等一下  大家先别激动
All right, wait! Just wait. Everybody just calm down. Okay?
要给我们的老友乔伊一个机会
Let's give our friend Joey a chance
解释他为何如此变态
to explain why he's such a big pervert!
我不是变态  好吗
No! I am  a pervert! Okay?
只是...我...其实...
It's just... I just... Kinda...
我可以帮他解释
All right, look! Look. I think I can explain this.
谢谢
Thank you!
乔伊是性爱狂
Joey's a sex addict.
什么  不  我不是
What?!!  No I'm not!!
没关系  很好  很好
It's okay! It's good! It's good.
这是一种病
It's a disease!
不  我才不是性爱狂
No! No! I am not a sex addict!
你明明就是
Yes you are!
这才能解释最近这一连串的事
That's the only way to explain all this stuff!
不  事实不是这样
No it isn't! No, it's not.
你也可以说出真相
Because you can also explain it with the truth!
什么真相
Well, what is the truth?
-怎么回事  -到底怎么了
- Yeah, what's going on? - What's going on?
我跟莫妮卡上床了
I slept with Monica.
听听大家怎么说
Well let's....let's see what everybody thinks of that?
天啊
Oh no!
你跟我老妹上床了
You slept with my sister?
对  不过只在伦敦发生过一次
Uh yes, but it was, we just did it once uh, in London.
这会让我开始抓狂
This is not good for my rage.
莫妮卡  这是真的吗
Monica, is this true?
当然是真的
Of course it's true!
否则怎么解释最近这些怪事呢
How else would you explain all the weird stuff that's been going on?
对  是真的
Yes it's true.
如果只发生过一次
Okay, but if it only happened that one time,
你的内裤怎么会出现在我们家
how come we found your underwear in our apartment the other day?
那条内裤是我那天在伦敦穿的
That was the underwear I was wearing that night in London.
对不对  莫妮卡
Right Monica?
我想留下来  当纪念品
I guess I wanted to keep it  as a souvenir.
天啊  莫妮卡
My God Monica!!
你确定吗  乔伊
Are you sure Joe?
你确定你不是性爱狂吗
Are you sure you're not just a sex addict?
不是  要是有人是性爱狂
No! If anyone's a sex addict here,
那也是莫妮卡  没错
it's Monica! Yeah. Yeah.
打从伦敦回来后  她就想再勾引我上床
She has been trying to get me back in the sack ever since London!
所以她才拍裸照给你
So that's why she gave you a naked picture of herself.
这样说得通
That makes sense!
-摄像机呢  -莫妮卡你说
- And the video camera? - Uhh, Monica?
我架好摄像机是为了引诱乔伊上钩
I guess I set up the video camera to try and entice Joey.
可惜我不吃这套
But sadly I could not be enticed.
难以置信  你还真留下了乔伊的内裤吗
Unbelievable! I mean you really kept Joey's underwear?!
为什么  你为什么这么做
Why? Why would you do that?!
因为我是莫妮卡  生性龌龊
I'm Monica. I'm disgusting.
我跟踪男人  还保留他们的内裤
I stalk guys and keep their underpants.
看来现在大家都清楚了
Well, I think we've all learned something
到底谁恶心谁不恶心
about who's disgusting and who's not. Eh?
好  现在我要开始吃鸡块了
All right, now, I'm going to get back to my bucket.
我只吃鸡皮  鸡肉你们随便拿
I'm only eating the skin, so the chicken's up for grabs.
你说得很有道理
I really thought you making a good point.
可惜后来被打断了
I mean y'know, until you got cut off.
那个莫妮卡哪里有病啊
Yeah, what's up with that girl Monica?
不知道  我不是和她一起来的
I don't know! I didn't come with her!
各位  各位  你们猜怎么了
All right everybody! Everybody guess what?
我说服保罗下周考试
I just convinced Paul to give us a test next week!
考试
A test?!!
开心点  有考试才有进步
Come on! Tests make us all better learners!
对了  应该考论述题
Oh yeah! We should have essay questions!!